{
    "subject": "Jacques_Doillon",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "La_Vengeance_d'une_femme",
    "human_readable": "Jacques Doillon created La Vengeance d'une femme.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6424850821495056,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Jacques Doillon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5610306859016418,
            "question": "When was La Vengeance d'une femme released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5086104273796082,
            "question": "Who were the main actors in La Vengeance d'une femme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5055126547813416,
            "question": "Who directed the film La Vengeance d'une femme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48583680391311646,
            "question": "Were there any awards associated with La Vengeance d'une femme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4677077531814575,
            "question": "What is the plot of La Vengeance d'une femme about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4333224594593048,
            "question": "What genre might La Vengeance d'une femme belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42286357283592224,
            "question": "Is Jacques Doillon a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3137255609035492,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Jacques Doillon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2833625078201294,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Jacques Doillon's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jacques Doillon created La Vengeance d'une femme.",
            "html": "yago_25633_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another film directed by Jacques Doillon?",
            "html": "yago_25633_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Jacques Doillon a filmmaker?",
            "html": "yago_25633_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might La Vengeance d'une femme belong to?",
            "html": "yago_25633_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25633_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "The triple is:\n\"Jacques Doillon created La Vengeance d'une femme.\"\n\nAnd the answer is:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"no\" }`\n\nThis is because, according to document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25633/re-ranker-msmarco/89.txt, it is stated that \"Next Jacques Doillon film: La Vengeance d'une femme (1990)\" but there is no information about him creating the film. The document only mentions that \"La vengeance d'une femme was entered into the 40th Berlin International Film Festival\" which implies that someone else created the film, not necessarily Jacques Doillon himself."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Jacques Doillon is associated with creating the film \"La Vengeance d'une femme\" (1990), as it mentions his involvement and details about the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}